本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 苦手 吹风   时间轴： 糖醋栗
校对： 锁链   后期： 小安
混乱之子前情提要
Previously on Sons of Anarchy:
这个是从亚伯的图画本里掉出来的
This fell out of one of Abel's coloring books.
他肯定是在贾克斯家里找到的
He must have found it in Jax's house.
- 信? - 莫林・阿什比
Letters? Maureen Ashby.
你觉得贾克斯读了?
And you think Jax read them?
肯定是贾克斯或者塔拉找到的
Had to be Jax or Tara who found them.
克雷 贾克斯 罗密欧・帕拉达
Clay, Jax, Romero Parada.
- 朋友们叫我罗密欧 - 每扎有两打
- Friends call me Romeo. - Got two dozen of each load.
70万是付给你现有的货的
That's 700 for your current stock.
大概够一半外加你的运费
It should cover half plus your transport payment.
我准备好毒品等你回去时带走
I'll have the coke ready for you for the run back.
你忘了告诉我我们要为盖林度集团运毒了?
You forgot to mention we'd be running coke for the Galindo Cartel?
我们投票是决定卖枪给他们
We voted in selling them guns.
我们会再投一次票的
We'll have another vote.
我要你支持我 这样才能通过
I want you to back me. It's the only way this passes.
如果我帮你 那你移交帮派时
If I do this, when you hand over the club
你得尽量让奥佩当主席 就这个条件
you push for president's patch to go to Opie. That's the deal.
我退出换你的毒品
My out for your drugs.
你们闻到烟味了?
You smell smoke?
你逼我的 我强烈建议你别再这么做
You pushed me to this, and I strongly suggest you don't do it again.
我有些好消息
I have some good news.
我们订婚了
We're engaged.
现在鲍比 派尼 祖斯反对
We got Bobby, Piney, Juice opposed.
其他人怎么说?
Where we at with the rest?
奇博斯知道我们需要这个
Chibs knows we need this
来达成对爱尔兰共和军的承诺
to fill our Irish commitment.
他会支持我们
He'll go our way.
蒂格和爽哥也是
Tig and Happy too.
还得要一票
Still need one more.
柯茨克? 戒过毒 我估计他会反对
Kozik? Ex-junkie. I'm thinking he's a no.
- 我们能争取到奥佩? - 有可能
- We any closer with Ope? - A little.
他明白集团这单快递送货的好处
He saw the benefit of having the cartel on speed-dial,
但他还没完全同意
but he's not there yet.
那你就得推他一把
Well, you need to get him there now.
奥佩能为我们争取到迈尔斯
Ope gives us Miles,
那样就是多数票了
that gets us the majority.
你还得去做做鲍比工作
And you need to work on Bobby.
太难了 别想阻止他散播负面情绪了
Very least, stop him from spreading woe.
- 你用那个? - 是啊
- You using that? - Yeah.
那是亚伯用旧的
It's Abel's old one.
那个不行了 买个新的
It's a piece of shit. Buy a new one.
- 你确定? - 是啊
- You sure? - Yeah.
我们应该把它存放好防止其中一个小子用的上
We should put it in storage just in case one of the guys needs it.
好的 钥匙在垃圾抽屉里
Okay. Key's in the junk drawer.
对不起
Sorry.
没事
It's okay.
我想谢谢你那晚上做的事
I just wanted to thank you for the other night.
你在适当的时候分享了好消息
You sharing the news when you did.
那绝对是经典一招
That was a class act.
- 那确实帮了忙 - 没什么
- It really helped. - Of course.
我很高兴你融入了这个大家庭
I'm so happy you're joining this family.
你本来就是个很棒的妈妈
You're already a great mom,
你还会成为一个很棒的妻子
you're gonna be a great old lady.
谢谢
Thank you.
能够抚养贾克斯是我这辈子遇到的最好的事情
Raising Jax was the best thing that ever happened to me.
我爱我的儿子
I love my son
就像我爱他的老爸
as much as I loved his old man.
嘿
Hey.
- 我觉得他可能该换尿布了 - 哦
- I think he might need a change. - Oh.
是吗? 你知道吗 这些其实是一次性的
You think? You know, these are actually disposable.
只要脱下来 换个新的
You just take them off, put a new one on.
真的?
Really?
现在我真觉得带孩子这个事对你真不容易
And here I thought this whole raising-kids thing was so hard on you.
哦 嚯 嚯
Oh, ho, ho.
你再不走就得在孩子的尿里洗澡了
You should just get out of here before you're swimming in baby piss.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
嗨
Hi.
- 再见 亲爱的 - 回头见
- Bye, honey. - See you later.
嘿
Hey.
你的医生朋友们怎么看这一切?
What do your doctor friends think of all this?
一个好外科大夫去做一个黑社会孩子的母亲?
The good surgeon being an outlaw baby mama?
我不清楚 我没问
I don't know. I don't ask.
跟你一起被绑架的朋友玛格丽特呢?
What about your kidnappy friend Margaret?
我知道她对我们的看法比较具体
I know she's got some very specific opinions about us.
玛格丽特和我一起工作
Margaret and I work together.
慢慢了解一些情况
Learned to navigate around the subject.
啊 你就是这么处理的?
Ah, is that how you deal with it?
假装它不存在? 围着它打转?
Pretend it doesn't exist? Move around it?
我真没时间回答一个接一个的
I don't have time for 20
消极且带攻击性的问题伽玛 直奔主题吧
Passive-Aggressive Questions, Gemma. Get to the point.
我问过了
I did.
我没有欺骗别人我是谁或者跟谁在一起
I don't lie about who I am or who I'm with
但我也不想把它当成很光荣的事
but I don't wear it like a badge of honor.
你应该的
Well, you should.
你争取到的
You earned it.
我的个人关系不是为了给自己加分
My relationship isn't about accruing points.
我不是在玩魔兽世界
I'm not playing "World of Warcraft."
哼嗯 我完全不知道那是什么意思
Hmm. I have no idea what that means.
意思是我们想法不一样
It means we think differently.
我得走了
I gotta go.
哦 对了 马上要动手术了
Oh, right. Back-to-back surgeries.
好吧 我就待这儿 住在大芝麻街
All right, I'll just be here, living large on Sesame Street.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见 妈妈
Bye, Mom.
嘿 呆鸟 是你大便的?
Hey, dickhead, you the one made pancakes?
- 是啊 - 打算弄干净吗?
- Yeah. - Gonna clean your shit up?
- 现在? - 是的 立刻
- Now? - Yeah. Now.
- 你以为让谁来? - 你妈妈和阿姨
- Who you think's gonna do it? - Your mom and aunt.
不是你的佣人
Ain't your maids.
我们得先把这些装起来
We should load these first.
不 去 他最恨乱糟糟
No, go. He hates messy.
死进去
Get inside there.
哟 哥们 把那球扔回来好吗?
Yo, Gomer. You wanna toss me that rock?
哟  金发帅哥 你大白天穿那么多?
Yo, Buckwheat, wanna keep your shirt on?
谢谢
Thanks.
- 嘿 玩球吗? - 今天不了 伙计
- Hey, you ball? - Not today, man.
怎么了 冲浪小子 还害怕小小的街球?
What's the matter, surfer dude, scared of a little 'hood ball?
来吧 10块1分
Come on, 10 bucks a point.
闭嘴 婊子 你根本没钱
Shut up, bitch. You ain't got no money.
扯淡
Bullshit.
你有多少?
How much you got?
大概 300块左右
Like, 300 and something.
好的 我和你 黑娃
All right, me and you, LeBrown.
一对一 赢的全拿走
One on one, winner takes all.
见鬼 好 我的柠檬脑袋混球
Shit, yeah, my lemon-headed sucker.
好 哦 看看这个
Yeah. Oh, look at this.
看看我的欢乐的小侏儒们
Look at my happy, little elves.
他们看来很不错 怎么装?
They look great. How do they hold?
能装10到16支 要看枪的
Hold between 10 and 16, depending on the gun.
重量跟车部件相似
The weight matches the car parts.
不错
Beautiful.
奇博斯从爱尔兰共和军那儿弄的规格
Chibs got the specs from the Irish.
- 他去哪儿了? - 别问
- Where is he? - Don't ask.
浴室 在搞定大便
Bathroom, working shit out.
文艺点说 所有处理过的食物
Literally. All that processed food.
见鬼 你还好吧 伙计?
Shit, you all right, man?
有点不对劲 便宜的墨西哥食物
Something didn't settle right. Cheap Mexican food.
看来杰克詹姆斯家的墨西哥卷不行
Chasing burritos with Jack and James probably didn't help.
祖斯 你能帮我振作起来?
Juicy, you're gonna hit me up?
绿茶和薄荷
Green tea and a mint colonic.
- 一点草药混合物 - 停 停 停 停
- A little herbal fusion. - Stop, stop, stop. Stop.
在我们了解所有人的选择之前
Before we clear anybody's passage,
先把这些木板箱做好
let's just get these crates built.
鲍比 你跟我一起 去瓦汉瓦
Bobby, you're with me. Wahewa.
要我做什么?
Why you need me?
- 因为我想你 - 要我一起吗?
- Because I miss you. - You want me with?
不不 我们没事 在这儿帮忙
No, no, we're good. Stay available.
也许还需要人装些弹药
May need somebody to haul some ammo.
装吧 婊子
D up, bitch.
别让他这么玩弄 拦住他
Don't give him that lane. Stop that.
哦! 哦 老天!
Oh! Oh, God!
# 回到头罩里变得很忙 说真的 #
Back in the 'hood Getting busy, for sheezy
你要让他继续侮辱你吗? 加油 伙计
You gonna let him shoot that shit over you? Come on, man.
18比12
Eighteen-12.
该死 布鲁 这沙滩白大战黑人的状况
Damn, Brew, this beach-white nigga
让你看起来像个傻逼
got you looking like Cleveland.
- 哈 哈 哈 - 确实
- Ha-ha-ha. - For real.
胡闹 伙计
That's bullshit, man.
- 抢钥匙! - 快!
- Get the keys! - Hurry up!
快跑! 走 走!
Get the hell out of here! Go, go!
# 我要让你知道我的力量 #
I'm gonna show you I got the power
你知道怎么开卡车吗?
Do you even know how to drive a truck?
把你的屁股挪过围墙
Get your ass over the fence.
# 我要让你看看谁是老大 #
I'm gonna show you who's the boss
# 你会付出代价的 #
You're gonna have to pay the cost
# 抓我的现行啊 #
Catch me on the run
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
# 戴上头罩什么都不容易 那是真的 #
Ain't nothing come easy in the 'hood That's for sheezy
# 为了我的工作 #
For my business
真操蛋!
You got to be shitting me!
# 在这世间 独自穿行 #
Riding through this world All alone
# 上帝带走你的灵魂 你独自一人 #
God takes your soul You're on your own
# 乌鸦径直飞过 划出完美的线条 #
The crow flies straight A perfect line
# 在恶魔的床上 奄奄一息 #
On the devil's bed Until you die
# 此生如是 你必须直视 #
Gotta look this life In the eye
混乱之子 第四季 第3集
罗密罗 "罗密欧" 帕拉达
Romero "Romeo" Parada.
前墨西哥军队指挥官
Ex-Mexican military commando
由乔斯・盖林度征募
enlisted by Jose Galindo
掌管他的集团战略执行单位
to head up his cartel's strategic enforcement unit.
集团还有战略执行单位?
The cartel has a strategic enforcement unit?
索诺拉的集团有两个
There are two Sonora-based cartels:
盖林度和罗布・索诺拉
Galindo's and Lobo Sonora.
六个月前整个地区开始血拼
Blood feud over the whole territory began about six months ago.
看不出停手的迹象
Shows no sign of stopping.
所以罗密欧需要枪支
And Romeo needs guns.
是的 我猜为了拿到酬劳
Yes, I'm guessing the Sons will be
混乱之子会给他们运毒
expediting the coke that pays for them.
- 贩毒? - 不是在他们的仓库里
- Dealing? - Not in their wheelhouse.
也许用摩托运回北加州
Probably muling blow back to Northern Cali.
- 见鬼 - 我们过去几年
- Shit. - We've been watching Galindo
一直监视盖林度 他有点精神变态
for the last couple years. He's a spunky little psychopath.
自从他招募了罗密欧 他们就为TJ和其他人
Since he hired Romeo, they've been giving TJ and others
努力提供钱和毒品
a hard run for money and drugs.
我们听说罗密欧在斯托克顿跟混乱之子会面了
We'd heard Romeo had reached out to the Sons in Stockton
但是不能确定他们怎么解决俄罗斯人的
but weren't sure how they'd fit with the Russians.
我猜他们最后达成了一致
Guess they figured that out.
这个是从一个加油站的监控镜头提取的
This was lifted from a gas station security cam
就在我美丽的出生地
outside of my beautiful birthplace,
莫得斯托的附近 两天前
Modesto, two days ago.
所以帕拉达回到镇子里来了 哼?
So Parada's back in town, hm?
是的 不过又消失了
He was. Off the grid again.
那现在怎么办?
So now what?
没人打入内部记载枪支运送记录
Without someone inside to document the gunrunning
我们要将混乱之子作为RICO法案的主要目标
...we need to make the Sons the primary RICO target.
所以现在 我的当地执法朋友
So now, my locally enforced friend,
我们开始执行B计划
we move on to plan B.
请这位乌鸦先生做线人
Engage Mr. Crow to create the ties that bind.
胡汉・卡洛斯・奥提茨
Juan Carlos Ortiz.
我需要你把他抓起来
I need you to pick him up.
那有什么用?
How does that help?
我们需要建立一个新的组织犯罪史
We need to create a history of organized crime,
过去和现在的
past and present.
祖斯是我们的联结点
Juice is our "now" connection.
我可以以违反释放协定为名逮捕他
I can pick him up on a release violation.
他是一家草药店的合伙拥有者
He's a part owner of a weed shop.
很好
Good.
但是你不能让他察觉到这么多
But you can't tip him off to any of this.
只能以本地事务威胁他
The threat must remain local.
你们想要我对他做什么?
What do you want me to do with him?
就让他知道你察觉到他的家庭关系了
Just let him know that you're aware of his family tree
而且你会再找到他
and that you'll be in touch.
好的 我马上过来
All right, I'm coming.
- 怎么了? - 是迈尔斯
- What's going on? - That was Miles.
- 貌似枪支有点麻烦 - 要我叫克雷吗?
- Some kind of hiccup with the guns. - Should I call Clay?
不 他跟鲍比需要好好谈谈
No, him and Bobby need some quality time.
呆在这儿 叫其他的菜鸟帮着搞定这些
Stay here, get the other prospects to help finish these up.
- 照顾好他 - 没问题
- Take care of him. - Absolutely.
你跟我们走 跟着小货车 我们走
You're with us. Follow in the van. Let's go.
我跟 克雷要你呆在这儿
I'm going with. Clay wanted you to stay here.
我不想做他的小弹药婊子 我不干
I'm not gonna be his little ammo bitch. I'm not gonna do it.
要是枪有问题 我得去
If there's a problem with those guns, I should be there.
好吧 蒂格
All right, Tiggy.
我知道你带我出来不会是因为我懂子弹
I know you didn't bring me out here for my vast knowledge of projectiles.
我想跟你单独谈谈
I wanted to talk to you alone.
想说什么就说吧 老大
Say what you gotta say, pres.
过去几年我们后受到的打击
The beating we took over these last few years,
你知道 让我们损失了很多
you know has set us way back.
生活的一部分 我加入帮派不是为了变得富有
Part of the life. I didn't join this club to get rich.
无关富有 但关乎生存
It ain't about getting rich, it's about getting whole.
帮派需要动力
This club needs an infusion.
你怎么让你儿子同意这些的?
How'd you get the boy to sign off on this?
毒品几乎杀了他的第一个孩子
Drugs nearly killed his firstborn.
他改变了
He's changed.
他陷的太深了 我
He's gone way inside. I
我不知道是什么推动了他 也许是时间
I don't know what pushed him. Maybe it was the time.
- 也许是我? - 我不知道
- Maybe it was me? - I don't know.
他不再是原来那个他
He's not the same guy.
好吧 他当然知道对帮派什么最重要
Well, he sure knows what's best for this club.
省省吧 我们不是在投票桌前
Kill the bullshit, we're not sitting around the table.
你是在向着门口猛冲
You're sprinting for the door,
趁它还开着赶紧塞满自己的口袋
stuffing your pockets before it slams shut.
我明白的
I get that.
但是贾克斯得到了什么好处?
But what does Jax get out of it?
知道吗?
You know what?
你要怎么想我无所谓 因为我不在乎
You think whatever the hell you want to about me, because I don't give a shit.
我唯一关心的是这个帮派的未来
My main concern is the future of this MC.
我告诉你贾克斯得到了什么
I'll tell you what Jax gets out of it.
我就是带你来谈这个
That's what I brought you to talk about.
不过 我希望这只是你跟我之间的事
Only thing is, I need for this to stay between you and me,
你明白吗?
you understand?
因为贾克斯不想任何人知道这个
Because Jax doesn't want anybody to know about this.
我要你保证
I need your word.
贾克斯想要退出
Jax wants out.
他有两个孩子 他有个爱着的妻子
He's got two sons, he's got an old lady he loves.
他不干了
He's done.
他支持运毒 你让他净身出户
He backs the drugs, you let him out clean.
是的
Yep.
那跟我有什么关系?
What's that got to do with me?
我想支持你取代我
You're the guy I endorse to replace me.
是啊 如果我投票支持毒品 你就...
Yeah, if I vote for the drugs, you'll...
无关投票
It's not about any vote.
我是在传位于你
I'm handing you the gavel
因为你是做这个工作的最合适人选
because you're the best guy for the job.
如果你想的话
If you want it.
我是在向你做出承诺
I'm giving you my word.
你想找查理 Horse?
You looking for Charlie Horse?
- 呃 是的 - 他出去了 在南边屋子
- Uh, yeah. - He's out in the south res.
上车跟着我
Get in your truck and follow me.
- 嘿 - 嗯
- Hey. - Mm.
我就想记住该怎么做
Just trying to remember how to do this.
把火点着香
You put the flame to the wick.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不去你的教堂了?
You stop going to your church?
当你被你自己的罪行埋葬时
When you're buried in your own shit,
那神圣之心似乎有点遥不可及
the Sacred Heart seems a little out of reach.
你总得相信些什么 韦恩
You gotta believe in something, Wayne.
你自己有多信?
Where you at with that?
保持不变的信仰
Same place I'm always at.
不 你不是 亲爱的
No, you're not, sweetheart.
我们想做到不变 但我们做不到
We wanna stay the same, but we can't.
我们越老
Older we get
就越变得不像我们希望自己变成的那样
the further away we get from who we think we are.
说够了吗 孔夫子?
Are we done here, Confucius?
- 是的 - 我们走
- Yeah. - Let's go.
在这儿等着 你看见塔拉过来 就敲一下门
Wait here. You see Tara coming, knock on the door.
哇哦 不是把? 你带我来是给你望风的?
Whoa. Really? You brought me here to be your goddamn spotter?
我得做完我自己开始做的事情
I'm finishing what I started.
见鬼
Shit.
好吧 你个聪明的小婊子
All right, you clever, little bitch,
你把钥匙藏哪儿了?
where'd you hide that key?
我很难过 宝贝 我们会没事的
I'm sorry, baby. We're gonna be okay.
我们走
Let's go.
海特・威尔默特 医学博士
试管婴儿专家
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
哦
Oh.
抱歉
Sorry.
塔拉要跟你见面吗?
Is Tara expecting you?
不 我 嗯...
No. I, um...
我只是在做些研究
I was just doing some research.
超音波解剖学与可行性的超声指导
"Sonoanatomy and Feasibility of Ultrasonographic Guidance...
相关术语以及在早产儿的应用
...in Term and Preterm Neonates."
是三部曲
It's a trilogy.
- 嘿 在这儿啊 - 嘿 韦恩
- Hey there. - Hey, Wayne.
- 昂瑟警长 - 呃 不再是了
- Chief Unser. - Uh, not anymore.
当然
Of course.
能够你谈一会儿吗?
Can I talk to you for a second?
- 我? - 好啊
- Me? - Yeah.
关于我的医疗保险
I got some questions about my HMO
以及新的治疗方法我有些问题
and these new treatments.
当然
Sure.
我会告诉塔拉你进来了
I'll tell Tara you're in here,
专注于你的新生儿三部曲吧
engrossed in the Neonatas Trilogy.
先生们 这边请
Gentlemen. This way, please.
我们到这儿来到底干什么?
What the hell we doing out here?
部族事务
Tribal matters.
而且 让我们有机会私下谈谈需求的增长
Also, it gives us a chance to talk privately about this increase in demand.
有问题吗?
Is that a problem?
人手不是问题 而是补偿
Labor, no. Compensation, yes.
我知道你们现在在把我们的弹药卖给墨西哥人
I know you're selling our ammo to the Mexicans now.
我们跟瓦汉瓦的交易是定好的
Our deal with the Wahewa is set,
跟我们卖给谁没关系
doesn't matter who we're selling to.
我没那么老土 克雷
I'm not living in a teepee, Clay.
集团对你来说风险很大
The cartel is a risk for you.
我知道你肯定拿我们的子弹卖了更高价
I know you gotta be charging more for our bullets.
我只想确保瓦汉瓦得到应得的利益
I just wanna make sure that the Wahewa get their piece.
老天
Jesus Christ.
温图语中有一个词 意思是 哀悼战争
There's a word in the Wintu language, means "mourning war."
我们死去的孩子们的家人向神寻求复仇的方式
Families of our dead sons ask the gods to choose their revenge.
他们选择了食人蚁这种缓慢的死法
They chose slow death by flesh-eating ants.
那真的是牛仔和印第安的做法 酋长
That's some real cowboy and Indian shit, chief.
这个一种终结的方式
It's about closure.
你在他步入到精神领域的过程中起到了作用
You play a part in his passing over into the spirit realm.
我等会儿回来
I'll be right back.
他们要把他留在这儿多久?
How long they gonna leave him out here?
我猜直到野餐结束吧
I guess till the picnic's over.
你准备让查理得到更多分成?
Are you gonna give Charlie his bump?
我是说 我们同样的子弹
I mean, we are charging the Mexicans
卖给墨西哥人贵了至少一半
50 percent more for the same ammo.
我给查理个鸟 因为就他能知道的
I'm gonna give Charlie dick. Because as far as he knows
我们卖个墨西哥人跟卖给其他人一个价钱
we're charging the Mexicans the same as we charge anybody else.
求你了
Please.
帮帮我
Help.
嘿你能听到我们说话?
Hey. Are you listening to us?
不
No.
不不 你一定听到了 是不是?
Well, you heard that, didn't you?
这里的神灵会被你气疯的
You're gonna piss off the gods.
我才懒得鸟他们
I don't give a shit about the gods.
我们的枪被一些小P孩偷了?
Someone is Stealing our guns is a hiccup?
你胡说什么?
You shitting me?
他们以为这皮卡里装满了酒
They thought the truck was full of booze.
里面还有一箱AR-15s
It had one case of AR-15s.
这些枪已经卖出去了的 混蛋
Those guns are already sold, asshole.
集团要在2天内拿到所有的货
The cartel is expecting all of them in two days.
- 这个我知道! - 你知道个屁
- I get it! - No, what you get...
你只会让一群贫民区的小屁孩玩弄 混蛋
...is jacked by a bunch of ghetto babies, asshole.
好了贾克斯! 先别计较这个!
All right, Jax! Let him go!
冷静点! 看上帝的份上!
Hang on! Save it for church!
让我们一起把枪支找回来
Let's just get the guns back.
他们不会公然在大街上使用那些武器
They're not gonna hit the streets with that.
他们肯定会找个地方想法卖了
They're gonna try and sell them.
你他妈闭嘴
Shut up.
在这块地方? 只有一个地方做那总生意
This 'hood? Only one place to do that.
- 法人区的维维卡 - 东西最好在那
- Vivica. French fence. - They better be there.
皮卡在几个小时前被偷了
Truck got jacked a couple hours ago.
我们估计你这应该是他们停留的第一站
We think you may be their first stop.
我看起来是做枪支买卖的?
Do I look like I buy guns?
不 但也许你认识那些孩子?
Well, maybe you know the kids.
布鲁斯特 他管他的伙计们叫变态
Brewster. He called his buddy "Frecks."
我的孩子够多了 没心情去认识更多的
I got enough kids. Don't need to know anyone else's.
听着 如果你们要iPad
Look, if you want iPads,
还是微波炉或是有机蔬菜
microwaves, or organic vegetables...
我将是你们的幸运女神
...I'm your Nubian goddess.
但枪支 那是肮脏的生意
But guns, that's dirty business.
不在我的经营范围 这附近的所有人都知道
Not my flow. Everybody around here knows that.
路德 范爵斯 送客
Luther, Vandross. Show them out.
如果它们确实涉足了你的经营范围
Well, if for some reason they do flow your way,
我们需要弄清楚
we need to know.
你唯一要弄清楚的是
The only thing you need to know is that
我的庄园被你们搞的透不过气
my soil is in desperate need of aeration.
那我们不影响这里了
Wouldn't wanna get between you and your dirt.
非常感谢
I appreciate that.
- 我可不相信她 - 暂时没有别的办法
- I don't believe her, man. - Got no choice.
会打草惊蛇的
Rock that boat, blow back on the whole neighborhood.
我老妈还有姨妈她们都有份
My aunt and mom included.
我靠 是他们!
Shit, that's them!
你守在着 看皮卡车会不会出现
Yo, stay here in case the truck shows up.
走走走!
Go, go, go!
# 当我还是个孩子时 #
# When I was a boy
# 我就憧憬我长大后的情景 #
I thought about the times I'd be a man #
# 我坐在瓶子里面 #
# I'd sit inside a bottle
# 幻想着我四处拥挤不堪 #
And pretend that I was in a jam #
# 在这个狭小的空间里 #
# In my lonely room
# 我可以专心幻想着那可爱的甜筒 #
I'd sit my mind in an ice cream cone #
# 你可以把我扔掉 因为我是如此渺小 #
# You can throw me if you wanna 'Cause I'm a bone #
# 我被丢掉时 #
# And I go
# 还会发出"噗噗噗"的声音#
"oop-ip-ip, oop-ip-ip," yeah #
# 如果我没有哭泣 #
# If I don't start cryin'
# 那是因为我根本就没有双眼 #
It's because that I have got no eyes #
- 小心! - 哦我靠!
- Look out! - Oh, Shit!
# 我的小狗已经被任由摆布 #
# And my dog lies hypnotized #
# 被一种我从未知道的光束 #
# Through a crack of light I was unable #
我们上
Let's go.
# 去寻找我的生活 #
# To find my way #
# 虽然被困其中 但我很快乐 #
# Trapped inside a night, but I'm a day
# 还能"噗噗噗"的响 #
And I go "oop-ip-ip" #
该死 如果条子发现了那些枪
Shit. Cops find our guns
他们肯定会追踪爽哥姨妈家里
they'll lead them right back to Happy's aunt's house.
嘿让我来对付
Hey, I got this.
靠边停下!
Pull over!
手举到我看的见的地方
Keep your hands where we can see them.
我们追!
Let's go!
呼
Whew.
请出示驾驶执照 谢谢
License and registration, please.
他死了
He's dead.
- 怎么回事? - 不清楚
- What happened? - Not sure.
他一直那样 喘了几口气就呜呼了
He came to, gasped a little bit, and just went out.
是啊 发生的很快
Yeah. It was quick.
家族会很失望的
Family's gonna be disappointed.
他应该至少再受两天的苦
He should've suffered at least another two days.
或许... 那些蚂蚁比你想象的要饿的多
Well, maybe the ants were a little hungrier than you thought.
或许吧
Yes.
就像我们所有人一样
Like all of us.
听着查理 我不知道你听到过什么
Look, uh, Charlie, I don't know what you heard...
或者你是怎么认为的  但...
...or what you think you might know, but, uh...
但我们和集团的生意
...we got the same deal going with the cartel
一点都不比和俄国佬做的多
as we had with the Russians.
我们不会让你蒙受一个子的损失
We're not making a dime more off your ammo.
我向你保证
You got my word.
好吧
Okay.
我们会尽快把订单完成
We'll push through with the order then.
我们的皮卡还有那些枪在哪?
Where's that truck and our guns?
什么皮卡?
What truck?
该死的 我可没拿你们那该死的枪
Damn, man. I ain't got your goddamn guns.
- 冲击试验? - 我看行
- Crash test? - Think so.
请允许我来 给我钥匙
Allow me. Keys.
- 老兄 拜托 - 玩的开心点
- Oh, man. Come on, man. - Have fun.
老兄拜托!
Come on, man!
放我出去 老兄!
Let me out, man. Let me out!
你们这些基佬想杀了我们吗?
You cracker-ass bitches trying to kill us?
有这打算 除非你们老老实实说出来
That's the plan, unless you start talking.
我都不知道你在说什么!
I don't know what you're talking about!
哦完了
Oh, shit.
- 不 不要! - 狗娘养的骗子!
- No, no! - Lying bitch!
嘿兄弟 你怎么回事? 听我说听我说!
Hey, man, what's wrong with you? Listen, listen, listen!
你在干什么啊? 你在...?
Yo, what are you doing? Yo, man, what are you...?
- 放我走吧 老兄! - 听着 听好了
- Let me go, man! - Listen to me. Listen to me.
这个家伙曾经抱了我一下就抱断我三根肋骨
Now, this guy here, he's cracked three of my ribs giving me a hug.
他会把你们的脸给撕碎的
He's gonna shatter your boy's face.
除非你们老实交代
Unless you Give it up.
- 该死的那好吧 - 听我说
- All right. Goddamn, man. - Just listen.
我们把枪卖给了维维卡
We sold it to Vivica.
Luther给了我们一半的钱
Luther gave us half the cash.
我们刚才去那就是拿剩下的一半
We were headed to get the rest when y'all spotted us.
钱就在杂物箱里
The money is in the glove box.
- 钱在这 - 我们把皮卡停在兰利市里
- It's here. - We unloaded the truck on Langley.
我打电话给迈尔斯
I'm calling Miles.
我就知道那个婊子在撒谎
I knew that bitch was lying.
要么就是这些混账 把他丢到后备箱里
Or these assholes are. Put him in the trunk.
给我起来!
Get up!
兄弟拜托 我们都招了!
Man, come on! We told you!
去找下那辆皮卡
Check on the truck.
等他出来 直接把他带来
Wait until he comes out, pull him over.
如果他有卡不能算违法
It's not a violation if he's got a card.
他现在已经正式释放了
He's on federal release.
山姆大叔从来没有认可过加州的大麻药用法律
Uncle Sam doesn't recognize Cali's medical-marijuana laws.
我们只针对奥提茨  有没有特别的原因
Is there any reason why we're just going after Ortiz, LT?
没什么特别的
Nothing specific.
我们先抓小鱼 然后慢慢钓大的
We start off small, we work our way up.
随时向我报告
You let me know.
请进
Come in.
- 手术顺利不? - 顺利
- Surgery went well? - Yes.
常规的膈疝而已
Routine diaphragmatic hernia.
这个给你的
Here you go.
仅供参考
References and other info.
兰格斯・伊曼纽尔医院和天道医院
Legacy Emanuel and Providence Hospital
都很希望能找你谈谈
are very interested in speaking with you.
哇哦 很感激你帮我做这些
Wow. Thank you for doing this.
我刚才打算把这些放你办公室的
I came by to drop them off earlier.
伽玛在这呢
Gemma was here in your office.
- 她有没有说为什么来? - 没说
- Did she say why? - No.
但我非常确信她当时是在找什么东西
But I'm pretty certain I interrupted her looking for something.
- 她看到这个了没? - 没
- Did she see this? - No.
或许... 她是在找一些孩子要用的东西
Well, she was probably just looking for something for the baby.
或许吧
Probably.
谢了
Thanks.
我听到那些护士们在说...
I've heard the nurses talking. Um...
你真的订婚了?
Are you really engaged?
是的
I am.
贾克斯知道你打算离开的事吗?
Does Jax know you're planning to move?
我还没告诉他
I'm not just yet.
- 塔拉你... - 我得留在这
- Tara. - I need to be here.
两个月前你闯进我的办公室
Two months ago you broke down in my office.
- 你要我帮你... - 我知道...
- You asked me... - I know, and...
我坚信那样做没错
I still feel that way,
但我不得不由贾克斯来决定这个
but I have to let Jax lead us out, Margaret.
这可能需要更久的时间 但...
It may take longer, but...
这是让我们一家全身而退的唯一方法
...it's the only way I get my whole family out clean.
更久可能意味着永久 你懂的
Longer can very easily turn into forever. You know that.
你好好考虑下
Please think about this.
这是我唯一能想到的
It's the only thing I think about.
我得准备去做手术了
I have to get ready for surgery.
嘿小子 放松点
Hey, hey, hey, easy. Easy, man, easy.
只是来找你老妈谈谈
Just wanna talk to your mom.
孩子们 没事的
It's okay, boys.
多谢你招待我兄弟
Appreciate you taking care of my crew.
他们看起来有点口渴
They looked a little thirsty.
我也不喜欢被白人小孩监视
And I don't like white boys spying on me.
长话短说吧 我们抓到了那些偷我们枪支的人
Yeah, well, we tracked down the crew that jacked our guns.
他们说把枪卖给了你
Said they sold them to you.
你们这些人他妈的是不是有病?
What the hell is it with you guys?
我没有你们那些破枪
I don't have your goddamn guns.
或许你的孩子们知道些什么
Maybe your boys know something.
是啊 孩子们你们怎么说?
Yeah, how about it, boys?
你们是不是瞒着老妈搞副业?
You taking on a little side biz mama don't know about?
你们这些蠢猪!
You idiots!
- 贾克斯小心! - 不! 住手!
- Jax! - No! Stop! Stop!
- 妈! - 喂! 趴下!
- Mama! - Hey, hey! Get down!
- 我靠 - 都他妈住手!
- Shit. - Knock it off!
我的天!
Jesus Christ!
你们这两个猪脑袋在想什么呢?
What the hell were you two cat-brained morons thinking?
我们是想给您个惊喜
It was supposed to be a surprise.
我们本想送您那部超级F-350
We was gonna get you that F-350 Super Duty.
我们知道您有多么喜欢那种皮卡
We know how much you love that truck.
我们都已经把它装饰成红色了
We even had a red one all picked out.
我深表歉意
My apologies.
把枪还给他们! 所有的!
Give them their guns! All of them!
刚才那枪声会把条子引过来的
Cops are gonna be here after that blast.
不 他们不会来
No, they won't.
这是给你们的补偿
For your troubles.
告诉爽哥我等下会送些西红柿给他老妈
Tell Happy I'll send his mom some tomatoes.
家庭会议 都进来!
Family meeting inside!
- 路德和范爵斯 - 快去 杀手先生
- Luther, Vandross! - Come on, killer.
马上过来!
I said now!
你看那老妈 伽玛和她比简直就是一淑女
That one there, she makes Gemma look like Donna Reed.
我瞬间对女人一点想法都没了
I'm suddenly feeling a little less dysfunctional.
- 是你 - 抱歉没和你打招呼
- Hi. - Sorry to barge in.
- 手头有事在忙? - 没有
- In the middle of something? - No. Just, um...
刚做好手术 只是些文件
...finished surgery. Just paperwork.
我刚才来过
I came by earlier.
是的 玛格丽特告诉我了
Yeah, Margaret mentioned that.
是啊 我知道她会告诉你
Yeah, I'm sure she did.
这个夹在亚伯的填色本里
This fell out of one of Abel's coloring books.
你知不知道他在哪找到的?
You have any idea where he might've found it?
那是什么?
What is it?
一个目录
A note.
关于一些信件的
Talks about some letters.
谁的信件?
Letters to whom?
你是不是藏了我的一些东西?
You hiding something from me?
我为什么要那么做?
Why would I do that?
这个原因你自己很清楚
Same reason you keep answering my questions with questions.
听起来你已经知道原因了
Sounds like you already know the answers.
不
No.
我不知道
I don't.
我知道的是...
What I do know...
那些信是约翰 特勒写的
...is that letters from John Teller...
如果我儿子读到那些信 他将会痛苦不堪
...would be very painful for my son to read.
为什么?
Why?
约翰当时爱上了莫林・阿什比
John was in love with Maureen Ashby.
那次我们去比尔法斯特的时候
When we were in Belfast...
我发现了他们之间有个孩子
...found out she had a kid with him.
于是那些陈年往事被激起千层浪
Stirred up all that old shit.
当时我也已经爱上了克雷
I had already fallen in love with Clay.
所以在托马斯死后
When Thomas died, uh...
我就再也不去忌讳这个
...I didn't care anymore.
我当时甚至都不隐藏点什么
I didn't even try to hide it.
那是个错误 把克雷推到了风口浪尖上
That was a mistake. Put Clay at risk.
对约翰来说 这是多么耻辱的事
It was humiliating for JT.
杰克斯对这些事毫无所知
Jax doesn't know any of that.
但如果他知道了 他肯定会和克雷隔阂很大
Him finding out could set things off with Clay again.
约翰当时伤透了我的心
John ripped me apart.
他在贝尔法斯特一直待了数月
Spent months at a time in Belfast...
就为了和她在一起
...with her.
丢下了我
Left me here.
一个人在这
Alone.
照顾他的孩子
With his sons.
抱歉
Sorry.
我爱他
I loved him.
像你爱贾克斯那样
Like you and Jax.
我才十九岁
I was 19.
那时他就是我的一切
He was my goddamn world.
这事对任何人都没好处
This ain't good for anybody.
你明白我的意思吗?
You understand me?
任它传播 对我们家庭最终都没好处
Wherever this leads, this is bad for our family.
噢噢 那太疯狂了
Oh, ho. That was crazy.
我看到自己拉出了我七岁时吞下的东西
I just saw some stuff in there I ate when I was 7 years old.
现在一身轻松 焕然一新啊
I'm like 100 pounds lighter. I'm a brand-new man.
嘿 你肠道彻底清洗过了
Hey, just got a full cleanse.
等等 什么? 好 回聊
Hang on. You know what? Sure, I'll call you back.
如果你们要光顾 我推荐绿茶哦
If you guys are heading in, I recommend the green tea.
双手扶墙 过去
Hands on the wall. Let's go.
有带卡
Got a card for that.
联邦政府才不鸟这个
The federal government doesn't give a shit.
你他妈逗我?
Is this some kind of joke?
你说呢?
Does that feel like a joke?
走
Let's go.
你们两个还好吧?
You boys still love each other?
嗯 没问题
Yeah. Cool.
这才是大团圆结局
It's all about the happy ending.
耶耶耶 走吧 来
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's go. Come on.
要投票
Got a vote to get to.
好的 来
All right, here you go.
什么回事?
So, what's going on?
嘿 我只是想和你聊会 就这样
Hey, I just wanna have a conversation, that's all.
你跟我律师聊去
You can do that with my lawyer.
噢 用不着你的律师
Oh, you don't need your lawyer.
我才不鸟你的草药店 伙计
I don't give a shit about the weed, man.
请坐
Please, sit down.
那你抓我干嘛?
So why'd you pick me up?
这是我和我爸在洛科威沙滩钓鱼拍的
This is me and my father fishing at Rockaway Beach.
啊 所以
Huh? Heh.
- 你是在昆士长大的对吧? - 嗯哼
Now, you grew up in Queens, right? Heh, heh.
没人会在洛科威钓鱼
Nobody fished at Rockaway.
除非你是想去烧瓶子针筒
Not unless you wanted to fry up bottles and syringes.
- 你不是昆士长大的 - 你想玩什么?
That ain't Queens. What's the game here, man?
- 你见过你爸爸吗? - 没
Do you ever see your father? No.
我可以给你安排
I can arrange that.
迈克尔・霍华德・科尔
Michael Howard Cole.
他是你爸
It's your daddy...
胡汉・卡洛斯
...Juan Carlos.
哼?
Huh?
从你的沉默中 我可以知道
By your silence, I'm assuming that...
你已经知道了
...you already knew.
我知道他是谁 我没见过他
I knew who he was. I never met him.
我不知道你能不能在照片上看出来 但是 呃
Now, I don't know if you can tell by this picture, but, um...
他是黑人
...he's black.
纯黑那种
Like, African black.
嗯
Yeah.
我受遗传了
I picked that up.
对
Yeah.
我不知道 你说如果帮派知道了
I don't know, you tell me. What would the club do if they found out that...
你是黑人会怎样?
...you were black?
嗯?你不知道?
Hm? You don't know?
我来给你描述一下
Let me break it down for you.
他们先把你赶出去 然后让你剥掉纹身
Well, first they'll pull your patch, then they make you scrape the ink.
如果运气好 你还能活着出去
Then if you're lucky enough, you'll walk out alive.
但对于萨门克罗来说 就当从来没你这个人了
As far as Samcro is concerned, you never even existed.
这些都是肯定的
So much for affirmative action.
- 你知道我帮派个屁 - 对 没错
You don't know dick about my club. Yeah, you right.
帮派我知道个屁
About dick, nothing.
但是你呢 惨了 啥都知道
But Leroy? Shit, everything.
祝你愉快
Enjoy your day.
那现在怎样?
So, what happens now?
我们都回家去
We go back home to our families.
我会保持联系的 兄弟
I'll stay in touch, brother.
墨西哥酒当午餐?
Mexican for lunch?
是啊 差不多
Yeah, something like that.
什么事?
What's going on?
我倒希望你告诉我呢 他会听你说的
I was hoping you could tell me. He listens to you.
谁?
Who?
克雷?
Clay?
他正带着我们走向深渊
You know, he is getting us involved in some very deep shit.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
你男人想让我们给集团运毒
Your old man wants us running drugs for the cartel.
帮里全部人都跟着他
And all those other drones at the table...
大家都会消亡殆尽的
...they're gonna follow him right down to that last little crumb.
跟他讲讲道理 伽玛
Talk some sense into him, Gemma.
怎样? 发生什么事了
So? What happened?
鸟事 他们头摆摆架势
It's nothing. Method Man just slapping his dick around.
- 真的? - 是啊
Yeah? Yeah.
你们给墨西哥人运毒?
You guys are running coke for the Mexicans?
什么?
What?
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
反正不是你
Not you.
你不需要知道
You don't need to know.
我们不该干这个
Drugs are not what we do.
你别跟我说要干什么
You don't tell me what we do.
还好吗?
Everything okay?
恩 我们来把事情解决了吧
Yeah. Let's just get this done.
我知道怎么解决你的问题
I had a cure for your disease
但你不听
But you threw it away
而且你说得很清楚 不让我插手
And you made it clear I was not welcome
嘿
Hey.
你真的觉得我们能处理好毒品的事吗?
You really think that we can handle the drug end of this?
我们可以的
I know we can.
你像克雷一样疯了
Getting as cocky as Clay too.
这不是坏事 伙计
That's not a bad thing, man.
你变得强硬了
You came out harder.
像帮派的领袖
Looking like a guy who can lead a club.
今天的破事 你都处理好了
That bullshit today, you handled it, man.
- 谢谢 - 我会投支持票的
Thanks. You got my vote.
还有迈尔斯 当我们做完集团的生意
And Miles. And when we're done with the cartel...
还有克雷下台了 你和我就是帮派的领袖
...and Clay is gone, it's you and me at the head of that table.
把帮派带回正轨吧
Get this back to the way it should be.
你同意吗?
You good with that?
# 这一切本来都会属于你 #
And all of this would've been
# 这一切本来就该属于你 #
All of this could've been yours
你们都有足够时间想清楚
You've all had time to think on this.
赞成或反对
Yea or nay.
我们和盖林度集团做生意
We get in business with the Galindo Cartel.
赞成
Yea.
他们信不过
I don't trust them.
反对
No.
赞成
Yea.
我赞成
I'm a yea.
反对
Nay.
No.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我反对
I'm a no.
支持正副会长
Backing my pres and VP.
赞成
Yea.
6个赞成 5个反对
Six, five.
通过
It passes.
# 我的否定和恐惧 #
My denial and fear
# 我所有的怨恨 我所有的眼泪 #
And all of my hatred And all of my tears
# 我所有不能归家的时候 #
All of the time That I couldn't go home
# 我所有独自悲凉的时候 #
And all of the times That I froze all alone
# 所有的悲惨 所有的谎言 #
And all of the sadness All of the lies
# 所有蒙蔽我眼睛的阴影 #
And all of the shadows That blackened my eyes
你要再利用我老婆跟我对抗
You ever try to end-run me through my old lady again...
我就毙了你
...I'll slit your throat.
# 在角落蜷缩吧 他们都在我脑海里 #
Now creep in the corner They're all in my head
# 所有被你变成噩梦的梦 #
All of the dreams That you made nightmares
# 所有沉默而喧嚣的眼神 #
All of the silence Deafening stares
# 所有不堪重负的船 #
All of the ships Who can't carry loads
# 被你在彼岸用愤怒之火焚烧 #
You wrecked in anger Upon distant shores
# 这一切本来都会属于你 #
All of this would've been
# 这一切本该属于你 #
All of this could've been yours
# 噢 这一切本来都会属于你 #
Oh, all of this should've been
# 这一切本来就该属于你 #
All of this could've been yours